legsjapan.com 2014-06-29

# Legs Japan Privacy

We understand that privacy is important to you, and we promise to look after your personal information. Any personal information you provide to us will only be used and recorded in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. **We will not sell or share any information about you to any other party.**

By providing legsjapan.com with your information, you consent to the collection and processing of such information in accordance with the terms of this Policy. 

We will only collect information about you if you willingly provide it. The information you provide which is about you is referred to as personal information. 

The details you provide may include your name, email address, or residence address. We may collect your IP (Internet Protocol) address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the website. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. Your IP address is also used to help identify you during a particular session and to gather statistical data. 

We will use this information to fulfill any order, to fulfill any of our services and to communicate with you when necessary. 

We will only keep your personal information for as long as necessary and consistent with the purpose for which you have given it to us. Except where needed to respond to a query from you or to fulfill an order, we will delete your personal information on request by you. 

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you - to obtain a copy of this personal information, please refer to the Contact page. 

Our website contains links to other websites. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites and we recommend you read the privacy statements immediately on entering other websites. This Policy applies only to information collected and used by us through the website.
